♪ Fly me to the moon ♪
♪ 带我飞向月球 ♪
♪ And let me play among the stars ♪
♪ 让我在群星间嬉戏 ♪
♪ Let me see what spring is like ♪
♪ 让我看看春天是什么模样 ♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars ♪
♪ 在木星和火星之上 ♪
♪ In other words, please be true♪
♪ 换句话说，请真诚以待 ♪
♪ In another words♪
♪ 换而言之 ♪
♪ I...♪
♪ 我... ♪
♪ I love♪
♪ 我爱 ♪
♪ You♪
♪ 你 ♪
♪ You, you, and you♪
♪ 你，你，还有你 ♪
The three of us?
我们三个？
Let's give it up for Rich.
让我们为里奇鼓掌。
That one never gets old. He's talking to me not you.
那个笑话永远听不腻。他是在跟我说话，不是跟你。
Beautiful voice, Captain.
声音真好听，机长。
So good.
太棒了。
You are terrible.
你真坏。
You know what I'm terrible at?
你知道我最不擅长什么吗？
Marriage.
婚姻。
I'm pretty good at first dates.
初次约会我倒挺在行的。
Hey, honey.
嘿，亲爱的。
- Oh, thank God. - I thought we missed you.
- 哦，谢天谢地。 - 我还以为我们错过你了。
I got your message.
我收到你的消息了。
Yeah, they changed the roster.
是啊，他们改了排班表。
When are you coming back?
你什么时候回来？
Babe, I'll send you a new schedule when I get it.
宝贝，我拿到新排班表就发给你。
Ben, I know you're hurting.
本，我知道你很难过。
We both are.
我们都很难过。
But you can't keep running away from that.
但你不能一直逃避这件事。
Hold on, babe.
坚持住，亲爱的。
Hey, Lisa, you found me something.
嘿，丽莎，你帮我找到活儿了。
There's a LA-Shanghai route, but I don't know, it's leaving soon.
有条从洛杉矶飞上海的航线，但我不太确定，航班很快就要起飞了。
All right, I'll take it.
行，我接了。
You won't have time to go home.
你没时间回家了。
Doesn't matter. I'll take it.
没关系，我拿着就行。
Hey, I got Nadine on the other line.
嘿，纳丁打另一条线过来了。
I'll call you back, all right?
我待会儿打给你，行吗？
Honey?
亲爱的？
- Mom, where are you? - Our son is sick, Ben.
- 妈，你在哪儿？ - 咱们儿子病了，本。
He needs you here.
他需要你在这儿。
- Oh, I gotta go. - Mom!
- 哦，我得走了。 - 妈妈！
- Nadine... - Sean's calling.
- 纳丁…… - 肖恩在打电话。
Ow. Sir? You can't smoke here.
哎哟。先生？这里不能吸烟。
Cinemas, planes, bars.
电影院、飞机上、酒吧里。
Now I can't even smoke outside without being harassed by the fun police.
现在连在外面抽烟都要被那些扫兴警察似的管着。
Come on. Sir.
来吧，先生。
The designated smoking areas are located right over there.
指定的吸烟区就在那边。
Fuck!
妈的！
Hey, Rich.
嘿，里奇。
It looks like I'm your right seat to Shanghai.
看来我是你飞上海的副驾驶了。
Been a while.
好久不见。
I heard you're hanging it up.
听说你要退休了。
Thank you. Here you go.
谢谢。给你。
Penny... Hey.
佩妮……嘿。
...you missed karaoke night.
……你错过了卡拉 OK 之夜。
I hear you sang that same song again.
我听说你又唱了那首老歌。
Damn. Did it work?
靠。管用了吗？
It always works.
总是管用。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Sorry, sir, please step this way.
抱歉，先生，请往这边走。
Hell.
该死。
I've got a random. Meet you guys at the gate.
我随机选了一个。咱们登机口见。
Go ahead. Go ahead.
你先走。你先走。
How you doing, Penny?
你好吗，佩妮？
Good. How are you?
挺好的。你呢？
You trust me to captain a plane.
你信任我当机长。
You worried about my toothpaste.
你却担心我的牙膏。
Any batteries or power banks?
有携带电池或充电宝吗？
Sir?
先生？
Uh, no.
呃，不。
Sure I can't get upgraded? I'm a gold member, you know.
真的不能升舱吗？我可是金卡会员。
I don't want to.
我不想。
You know how I get with flying.
你知道我坐飞机时是什么样。
Okay, look, do we have to do this here?
好吧，我们非得在这儿谈这个吗？
- I don't want to. - Right here? Tell you what.
- 我不想。 - 就在这儿？我跟你说。
You don't get it.
你不明白。
The plane is bigger to Shanghai... No, they're not.
去上海的飞机更大……不，不是的。
...than the ones you've previously been on. Okay?
……比你之前坐过的那些都要好，明白吗？
That's something, right? You folks okay?
这总归是好事，对吧？你们还好吗？
Yeah, it's fine. My daughter doesn't like flying.
嗯，没事。我女儿不太喜欢坐飞机。
You know what's more dangerous than flying on an airplane?
你知道比坐飞机更危险的是什么吗？
Hippos.
河马。
No way. You made that up.
不可能。你瞎编的吧。
Google it.
上网查查。
You're gonna be fine.
你会没事的。
Unless someone smuggles a hippo onboard.
除非有人偷运一头河马上飞机。
Are you, like, a captain?
你，呃，是机长吗？
No, I'm a first officer.
不，我是副驾驶。
It's my job to make sure the captain flies straight.
我的职责是确保机长飞得笔直。
Aren't you too old not to be a captain?
你这个年纪还没当上机长，不觉得太老了吗？
- Cora!
- 科拉！
Tough, huh? Yeah.
挺难熬的，是吧？是啊。
Uh, well, Cora... sometimes in life... you gotta take a few detours to get where you're going.
呃，那个，科拉……有时候人生就是这样……得绕点弯路才能到达目的地。
You ever had to take a detour?
你曾经不得不绕道而行吗？
No, I'm extremely punctual.
不，我向来准时。
Good girl.
好姑娘。
She's tough.
她很强硬。
- I know, thank you. - Cora.
- 我知道，谢谢。 - 科拉。
Cora, Cora, Cora, look. Look what Mama got me.
科拉，科拉，科拉，你看。看妈妈给我买了什么。
Hey, guys. Look, look.
嘿，各位。快看，快看。
Could that thing be any louder?
那玩意儿能再吵点吗？
I know. Cool, right?
我知道。很酷，对吧？
And I got a new battery for this.
我还给它换了个新电池。
Okay, there we go.
好了，搞定了。
Just put a pet chip in his neck.
只是在他脖子里植入了宠物芯片。
- Uh... - Cora, do you mind?
- 呃…… - 科拉，你介意吗？
I was doing something. I'll give it back.
我刚才在忙事情。我会还回去的。
Just hang on.
再等一下。
The password's his birthday.
密码是他的生日。
Listen, Cora, honey, we're gonna need you to look out for your brother on this trip, okay?
听着，科拉，亲爱的，这次旅行你得照顾好你弟弟，好吗？
Step-brother.
继弟。
- That's it. - That's the last of this.
- 就这些了。- 这是最后一件。
Load it up.
装上去吧。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Northeastern Airlines Flight N-140 to Shanghai - will now begin boarding. - Hey, hey!
东北航空飞往上海的 N-140 次航班——现在开始登机。- 嘿，嘿！
Don't you dare puke on me, bro.
你小子可别吐我身上，兄弟。
I'll drop your drunk ass right here.
信不信我把你这个醉鬼直接扔这儿。
I'm not playing, Hutch.
我可不是闹着玩的，哈奇。
Oh gosh, Esports.
哦天哪，电竞啊。
Playing video games isn't a real sport.
打电子游戏哪算得上真正的运动。
It's a bunch of losers kicking it in Mommy's basement with bags of Doritos and... Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
不过是一群窝在妈妈家地下室的失败者，抱着多力多滋薯片袋……哦，抱歉，失陪一下。
Ooh. What's up, Esports?
哟，电竞圈的朋友们好啊？
Let go. Get your hands off her!
放开她！把你的手拿开！
Whoa. Okay. Sorry. He's just a little drunk.
哇，好吧，抱歉。他只是有点醉了。
Ooh! She's feisty. I like it.
哦！她挺泼辣的，我喜欢。
Don't touch her.
别碰她。
What are you gonna do about it, Captain Keyboard?
键盘机长，你打算怎么办？
Hutch, get your disrespectful dumbass in line.
哈奇，你这不尊重人的蠢货给我排好队。
Is this how we talk to a lady?
我们就是这样跟女士说话的吗？
Coach, I got this-- Shut up, Jesse.
教练，我来处理——闭嘴，杰西。
Now, this is not how we represent ourselves on my team.
现在，在我的团队里，我们可不是这样表现自己的。
My apologies, Miss.
抱歉，小姐。
Excuse you.
你说什么？
I should have been upgraded.
我本该被升舱的。
Re-circ fan is written up.
再循环风扇已登记故障。
We can't legally depart until they fix it.
在他们修好之前，我们无法合法起飞。
I just reset it.
我刚重置了它。
Doesn't mean it won't crap out again later.
但这不代表它之后不会再出故障。
Hi. Welcome.
嗨，欢迎。
Just to the right.
往右边走。
You made us wait long enough.
你让我们等得够久了。
What's up, bro?
怎么了，兄弟？
Yeah, okay. There we go.
好的，好了。我们开始吧。
Yeah. Here you can... Hey, I'm fine.
嗯。你在这儿……嘿，我没事。
Let's sit down.
我们坐下吧。
Come on. Let's sit down.
来吧，坐下。
You want to strap in?
您想系好安全带吗？
Good afternoon, passengers.
各位乘客，下午好。
My name is Penny, and on behalf of Northeastern Airlines, I'd like to welcome you aboard... Coming through. Excuse us. And don't let us interrupt.
我是潘妮可，代表东北航空欢迎您搭乘本次航班... 借过一下，抱歉打扰了。不用在意我们。
Sorry. We were never here.
抱歉，我们从来没来过这里。
Sir, would you please put your seat back up?
先生，请您将座椅靠背调直好吗？
Why sure. I would like to welcome you aboard Flight N-140... What's your social media?
当然可以。欢迎您搭乘 N-140 次航班……您的社交媒体账号是？
...departing from LAX and arriving at Shanghai.
……从洛杉矶国际机场起飞，目的地上海。
- Thank you. - We'll be beginning our departure procedures shortly.
- 谢谢。 - 我们即将开始起飞程序。
So, at this time, please take your seats, and make sure your seat belts are securely fastened.
现在，请各位就座，并确保安全带已系好。
Northeastern 140, you will depart today from runway 24-L.
东北航空 140 号航班，今日将从 24L 跑道起飞。
Before Takeoff Checklist.
起飞前检查单。
Flaps.
襟翼。
Where do you think they're set?
你觉得他们设定在哪里？
I just need a response.
我只需要一个答复。
You do know, Ben, that the FAA has us confirm flaps over and over only because those idiots flying Delta 1141 were so busy yakking about which flight attendant they wanted to bang,
本，你该知道，联邦航空局让我们反复确认襟翼，全是因为达美航空 1141 航班那帮蠢货光顾着扯淡该睡哪个空姐，
they forgot to check them.
结果忘了检查。
Captain, I just need a response.
机长，我只需要一个答复。
Flaps are five, Ben.
襟翼五度，本。
Same place as the last three times we checked them.
和之前检查的三次一样，没变化。
Northeastern 140, you are cleared for takeoff, 24-L.
东北航空 140，允许起飞，跑道 24 左。
Clear for takeoff 24 left, Northeastern 140.
获准起飞，24 左跑道，东北航空 140 号航班。
See you guys. Captain.
回头见，机长。
It looked like you wanted to take a swing at me over that flap check.
刚才检查襟翼时，你看起来真想揍我一顿。
That wouldn't help my career any.
那对我的职业生涯可没半点好处。
Isn't that how you got bounced out of the Air Force?
你在空军被开除不就是因为这个吗？
Well, that senior officer had it coming.
哼，那个高级军官活该。
You, you're just, you're annoying.
你，你就是招人烦。
Blew your pension and your benefits.
你的养老金和福利全没了。
That's tough with a wife and young kids.
有老婆孩子要养，这确实不容易。
Had to catch on with some shitbag commuter airline and now you're in that seat when, of course, you should be in mine, and thinking you can't afford to break any more rules.
只能在一家烂透了的支线航空公司混日子，现在你坐在那个位置上，而本该是我的位置。你觉得再也担不起违反任何规则的后果了。
Well, Ben,
好吧，本，
I'm sure not gonna tell.
我肯定不会说出去。
So I could have popped you one and gotten away with it?
所以我当时揍你一顿也能脱身？
I'd rat you out.
我会告发你。
I know you would.
我知道你会。
No ice? Mmm-hmm.
不加冰？嗯哼。
What's up?
怎么了？
Not a lot.
没什么。
My granddaughter lives in Shanghai.
我孙女住在上海。
Awesome.
真棒。
Ben, um, I just wanted to check in on how your son's doing.
本，呃，我只是想问问你儿子的情况。
Heard he's been pretty sick lately.
听说他最近病得不轻。
Must be tough on your wife, especially when you're working and all.
你妻子肯定很辛苦，尤其是你还在工作的时候。
Yeah, well, Nadine's family lives nearby.
是啊，好在纳丁的家人就住在附近。
They help out when I'm gone.
他们在我离开时会帮忙。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Oh, damn it.
哦，糟了。
Statistics say that turbulence has never brought a plane down.
统计数据显示，湍流从未导致过飞机坠毁。
Is that supposed to be comforting?
这算是安慰吗？
I'm fine. I just spilled my gin and tonic when I really need it most.
我没事。只是在我最需要的时候，把金汤力洒了。
Hi, sir.
先生，您好。
Hey, take a guess what I need.
嘿，猜猜我需要什么。
I'm sorry. We're out of earplugs.
抱歉。我们没耳塞了。
That's perfect.
真是太好了。
Just perfect.
好得不能再好了。
What, you're gonna ration out the toilet paper, too, huh?
怎么，你还要定量分配厕纸吗？
You guys are unbelievable!
你们这些人真是不可理喻！
Sir, you can't do that!
先生，你不能这么做！
I can't hear you.
我听不见你说什么。
Yeah.
对。
What?
什么？
Way out of your league.
你配不上她。
Oh, no. No, I wasn't.
哦，不。不，我没有。
Wait. Really?
等等，真的假的？
She's a solid nine.
她绝对有九分。
Hate to break it to you, but you're a five.
真不想打击你，但你只有五分。
Maybe you could scrub up to a six, but that's being generous.
也许你收拾一下能到六分，但这已经是往高了说了。
Oh.
哦。
I'm getting destroyed by Betsy Ross back here.
我在这后面被贝琪·罗斯彻底打败了。
Wait, what if I've got a great personality?
等等，万一我有个很棒的性格呢？
You don't.
你没有。
Oh.
哦。
Cora, honey.
科拉，亲爱的。
Look, I know change is scary, okay?
听我说，我知道变化很可怕，好吗？
But Finn really looks up to you.
但芬恩真的很崇拜你。崇拜你。
So would it kill you to be just a little nicer?
对别人好一点能要你命吗？
Hey, it's me.
嘿，是我。
Cora.
科拉。
Where's Mom and Dad?
爸妈在哪儿？
They went to the pool for a swim.
他们去泳池游泳了。
There's a pool on the plane?
飞机上还有泳池？
Yeah. Yeah, it's back there.
有啊，就在后面。
Hey, little man, can't you find your seat?
嘿，小家伙，找不到座位了吗？
Oh, you into gaming, huh?
哦，你也喜欢玩游戏啊？
Right. You wanna show me how it's done?
是吗？想教教我怎么玩？
Yeah? Come on. Here.
行啊？来，拿着。
Okay. Your right hand is right here...
好。你的右手放这儿。
I am canceling master warning for forward cargo fire. Confirm.
我正在取消前货舱火警的主警告。确认。
Confirmed.
确认。
Let's do the memory items forward cargo fire.
执行前货舱火警的记忆项目。
Copy that. Forward cargo fire switch on.
收到。前货舱火警开关已打开。
Confirm. Confirmed.
确认。已确认。
Fire bottle discharge on.
灭火瓶已释放。
Confirm. Confirmed.
确认。已确认。
- Pan, pan, pan. - Northeastern 140.
- 呼叫，呼叫，呼叫。 - 东北航空 140。
We have a fire indication in our forward cargo bay and smoke has been detected.
我们前货舱出现火警指示，并检测到烟雾。
We require a heading to the nearest suitable airport, Northeastern 140.
我们需要前往最近合适机场的航向，东北航空 140。
Northeastern 140, this is KZAK Oakland.
东北航空 140，这里是 KZAK 奥克兰。
Your nearest airport is Guam International.
你们最近的机场是关岛国际机场。
Four hundred nautical miles south.
南边四百海里。
Let's get the captain back here.
让机长回来吧。
Roger.
收到。
- Roger, KZAK. - Northeastern 140.
- 收到，KZAK。 - 东北航空 140。
We are now direct Guam descending at 10,000 feet, Northeastern 140.
我们正在关岛直接下降至一万英尺，东北航空 140 号航班。
You okay, honey?
你还好吗，亲爱的？
Yeah, I'm fine.
嗯，我没事。
Ben, what do we have here?
本，我们这儿是什么情况？
Forward cargo fire.
前货舱起火。
We've completed the memory items.
我们已经完成了记忆项目。
Fire bottles aren't discharging.
灭火瓶无法释放。
I've declared an emergency.
我已宣布紧急情况。
We're descending to 10,000, redirecting to Guam International.
我们正在下降至一万英尺，改航关岛国际机场。
Get down there. Put it out.
下去吧。把火扑灭。
Roger.
收到。
Dad?
爸？
Dad? Are you in there?
爸爸？你在里面吗？
The fire turned into an explosion.
火焰变成了爆炸。
What the hell?
搞什么鬼？
We lost the cabin.
机舱失压了。
This isn't getting any better.
情况并没有好转。
Taking her down.
把她放下来。
Come on! Come on, grab them.
快！快，抓住它们。
Put it on, come on.
穿上它，快点。
Put this on. Okay?
把这个戴上。好吗？
Rich, put your mask on.
里奇，把你的面罩戴上。
Ben, we're gonna be level at 10,000 before you can even get that on.
本，我们会在你戴好之前就降到一万英尺高度。
Zoe, get your mask!
佐伊，戴上你的面罩！
11,000, for 10,000.
11,000，换 10,000。
Thousand to go.
还差 1,000。
Level 10,000.
高度 10,000。
I see 10,000.
我看到 10,000 了。
We're stable. Instruments responsive.
我们保持稳定。仪表响应正常。
Take the aircraft. I'm gonna make a PA.
你来操控飞机。我去做个广播通知。
My aircraft. Confirmed.
我来操控飞机。确认。
Your aircraft. Confirmed.
你来操控飞机。确认。
Folks, this is the captain speaking.
各位乘客，我是机长。
We have a fire in the cargo hold.
货舱发生火灾。
We've descended to a safe altitude and diverted to Guam International Airport.
我们已下降至安全高度，改降关岛国际机场。
It's very important that everybody remain calm.
请大家务必保持冷静。
Excuse me. Excuse me.
打扰一下。打扰一下。
I'm coming straight back.
我马上就回来。
We need all of you to follow your flight attendant's instructions... One second.
请各位听从乘务员的指示……稍等一下。
...as we get passengers near the affected area moved to safer seating.
……我们将协助受影响区域附近的乘客转移至更安全的座位。
Lisa.
丽莎。
There are more seats at the back!
后面还有更多座位！
This way, sir! Go, go!
这边请，先生！快，快！
No, no! Don't move unless you have to!
不，不！非必要不要走动！
Lisa!
丽莎！
Clear the passage!
让开通道！
My parents!
我的父母！
Not now. Stay here.
现在不行。待在这里。
We've lost engine one.
一号引擎失效了。
Sir, you can't do that!
先生，您不能这么做！
You're worried about this?
你在担心这个？
Get back to your seat right now!
立刻回到您的座位上！
Flight controls don't respond.
飞行控制器无响应。
Hydraulics are gone.
液压系统已失效。
Don't tell me what's broken.
别告诉我哪里坏了。
Tell me what still works on this jet.
告诉我这架飞机上还有什么能用。
You have manual cables to the outboard ailerons, elevator and rudder.
您有通往外侧副翼、升降舵和方向舵的手动钢索连接。
Let's get to it.
我们开始吧。
- Mayday, Mayday, Mayday! - Northeastern 140.
- 紧急求救，紧急求救，紧急求救！ - 东北航空 140 号。
We lost engine one.
我们失去了一号引擎。
140, Guam International is still the closest option.
140，关岛国际机场仍是最接近的选择。
We need something closer.
我们需要更近的地方。
140, we have nothing. You're over open ocean.
140，我们什么也没有。你们在公海上空。
Help us! Help!
救救我们！救命！
Instrument needles all rolling back to zero.
所有仪表指针全部归零。
We're on standby instruments.
我们切换至备用仪表。
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday!
求救，求救，求救！
This is Northeastern 140.
这里是东北航空 140 号班机。
We've lost power. Captain, we lost the radio.
我们失去了动力。机长，无线电也断了。
Stop the APU. Roger.
关闭辅助动力装置。收到。
It's okay. Just hold on, okay?
没事的。坚持住，好吗？
Hit it again.
再试一次。
- Nothing. - Again!
- 没什么。 - 再来一次！
APU is not coming up. We're at 6,000 feet.
APU 没有启动。我们正在六千米高空。
Try manual deployment of RAT.
尝试手动展开 RAT。
Ram Air Turbine. Confirmed.
冲压空气涡轮。确认。
Ram Air Turbine working. Instrument's back online.
冲压空气涡轮已启动。仪表恢复正常。
Relight the engine.
重新启动引擎。
Ignition.
点火。
Hit it again.
再试一次。
No!
不！
Dad! Where are you?
爸爸！你在哪？
No, no, no. Wait, wait. Come here.
不不不，等等，等等。过来。
Let me go! Let me go!
放开我！放开我！
We'll be all right.
我们会没事的。
Try it again.
再试一次。
It's not working.
还是不行。
We don't have enough airspeed to relight.
我们的空速不够，无法重新点火。
And no breathing room to dive for more.
没有喘息的空间去尝试俯冲。
We're gonna ditch.
我们要迫降了。
Start dumping the fuel.
开始排放燃油。
We're giving up on the relight?
我们放弃重新点火了？
Do it! Do it now! Dumping fuel.
动手！马上动手！放油！
This is the captain speaking.
我是机长。
Brace for impact.
准备应对冲击。
- Brace! Brace! - Heads down! Stay down!
- 抱头！抱头！ - 低头！保持低头！
Brace! Brace! Heads down!
抱紧！抱紧！低头！
Okay, okay. Get down! Get down!
好的，好的。趴下！趴下！
Ben, I want altitude and airspeed callouts every thousand feet.
本，每下降一千英尺报一次高度和空速。
3,000 feet, airspeed 220.
三千英尺，空速 220。
Too damn fast.
太快了。
I have a visual reference to swells.
我能目测到涌浪。
We gotta come right.
我们必须右转。
Rich, the checklist says we just parallel with the swells.
里奇，检查单上说我们只需与涌浪平行。
Swells aren't that bad.
浪头没那么糟。
I want all the headwind I can get to slow vertical down rate.
我需要尽可能多的逆风来减缓垂直下降速度。
Rich, if we go wing low and catch a tip, we're gonna cartwheel.
里奇，如果我们机翼压低卡到擦到浪尖，就会翻机。
And if I hit the water too fast, we're done for sure.
但要是入水速度太快，我们也必死无疑。
Just tell me which way the wind is blowing those swells.
告诉我风正把那些涌浪吹向哪个方向。
Rich, turn the airplane.
里奇，转动机身。
We're gonna land parallel to the swells.
我们要与涌浪平行降落。
We gotta come right 30 degrees. Confirm?
我们需要右转 30 度。确认吗？
Confirmed.
确认。
Bug that heading for me.
这个航向我负责。
Roger that.
收到。
2,000 feet. Airspeed 190.
高度 2000 英尺，空速 190 节。
You want flaps? As much as you can give me.
你要襟翼？能给我多少就给多少。
Flaps at maximum.
襟翼已放到最大。
1,000 feet. Airspeed 180. Still too fast.
高度 1000 英尺，空速 180 节，还是太快了。
Airspeed 170.
空速 170 节。
Landing gear up.
起落架收起。
APU fire suppression.
APU 灭火系统启动。
Watch your wings.
注意机翼。
300 feet.
300 英尺。
Airspeed still 170. Ben... move your seat all the way back.
空速仍 170。本……把座位调到最靠后。
Tighten your harness.
收紧安全带。
Rich, keep that wing up.
瑞奇，把机翼稳住。
I'm gonna bug you left 10 degrees.
我将向左偏 10 度给你报个点。
Tail down.
机头下沉。
Tail down. 100 feet.
机头下沉。高度 100 英尺。
Come on, girl, work with me.
加油，伙计，配合我。
Ben, move your seat all the way back. Do it!
本，把你的座椅调到最靠后。快！
Brace for impact!
准备撞击！
Oh, shit!
哦，糟了！
Help me!
救命！
Help!
救命啊！
Please!
拜托了！
- Somebody! - Help!
- 来人啊！ - 救命！
Somebody!
来人啊！
Help!
救命！
Rich!
里奇！
Wake up, Rich.
醒醒，里奇。
You did it.
你做到了。
If it wasn't for that coral reef, we'd be popping champagne right now.
要不是那片珊瑚礁，我们现在就该开香槟庆祝了。
You okay? Yeah.
你还好吗？嗯。
Okay.
好的。
Hey! Hey.
嘿！嘿。
You stay here, okay? And I'll be right back.
你待在这儿，好吗？我马上回来。
Okay, okay. Okay?
好的，好的。可以吗？
Oh, my God. Rich!
哦，天哪。里奇！
Grab him by the arms.
抓住他的手臂。
I'll try to get him loose, okay?
我试着把他弄出来，好吗？
One, two, three.
一、二、三。
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
Stop! That's not going to work.
停！这样行不通。
Hey.
嘿。
You're gonna be okay, Rich.
你会没事的，里奇。
We're gonna get you out of here.
我们这就带你出去。
Guys, we don't have much time.
各位，我们时间不多了。
Easy, Rich. Your leg's pinned.
别动，里奇。你的腿被卡住了。
- Crash ax. - What?
- 破门斧。 - 什么？
Don't even think about it.
想都别想。
No, you're not taking my leg. Not yet.
不，你休想截我的腿，现在还不是时候。
You can use it to pry me out.
你可以用它来撬开我。
Lisa.
丽莎。
Lisa!
丽莎！
Hey, little guy. Hey, hey.
嘿，小家伙。嘿，嘿。
Okay? Yeah? Okay.
好了吗？嗯？好了。
I have to get this off.
我得把这个脱掉。
Okay. All right, all right.
好了，好了，好了。
You're okay.
你没事。
Come here. Look at me. It's okay. Yeah?
过来，看着我。没事的，好吗？
Hello? Anybody?
喂？有人吗？
Hello?
喂？
Hello! Hello, anybody?
喂！喂，有人吗？
I'm here! Hey.
我在这儿！嘿。
Hold on.
等等。
- Okay. Yeah. - Someone's here?
- 好吧。是啊。-有人来了吗？
Someone here.
有人来了。
The nice lady. She's gonna come.
是那位好心的女士。她就要进来了。
She's gonna help us. Yeah? She knows what to do.
她会帮我们的。是吗？她知道该怎么做。
- Okay. - Yeah.
- 好的。- 是的。
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
呼吸，呼吸，呼吸。
It's okay.
没事的。
It's not coming free.
这不是免费的。
You're losing a lot of blood.
你失血太多了。
Guys, we have to move fast.
各位，我们得快点行动。
He's trapped.
他被困住了。
There's no other way.
没有别的办法了。
He's gonna bleed to death.
他会失血过多而死。
Ben, it's no good.
本，这样不行。
Don't be a chump.
别犯傻了。
Either way, I'm done and I'm exactly where I belong.
无论如何，我已经结束了，我正属于我该在的地方。
Don't give me that "where I belong" crap.
别跟我扯什么“该在的地方”这种鬼话。
You stay here, you die. Get out. Both of you.
你留在这里，会死的。出去。你们两个都出去。
Lock the door.
锁上门。
If that's open when this water breaks in, we'll flood the entire flight deck and drag everybody to the bottom.
如果这里一旦被水冲开，整个驾驶舱都会被淹没，所有人都会沉入海底。
I'm taking your leg.
我要截断你的腿。
You won't save any lives by drowning in here with some dickhead who always refuses to follow simple protocol.
跟一个永远不肯遵守基本规程的混蛋一起淹死在这里，救不了任何人。
It's your plane, Ben.
这是你的飞机，本。
I'm not leaving you, Rich.
我不会丢下你的，里奇。
I'm not leaving you.
我不会丢下你。
Confirm.
确认。
Confirmed. Go home, Ben.
确认。回家吧，本。
Be with your son.
陪着你儿子。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Ben, the ELT. Check the ELT.
本，应急定位发射器。检查一下应急定位发射器。
Honey. Oh, honey.
亲爱的。哦，亲爱的。
It's okay.
没关系。
Do you want to come and sit down?
你想过来坐下吗？
Penny.
佩妮。
Help me.
帮我。
Lift her up.
扶她起来。
You okay? Yeah? Yeah.
你没事吧？还好吗？嗯。
Declan.
德克兰。
Declan. Declan, wake up!
德克兰。德克兰，醒醒！
Declan, wake up!
德克兰，快醒醒！
Shit.
该死。
What the fuck is happening?
这他妈到底怎么回事？
Wait, are you all right? The kids.
等等，你没事吧？孩子们呢。
Fuck. We got to get out of here.
该死。我们得离开这里。
No! Declan, don't!
不！德克兰，别！
♪ Fly me to the moon♪
♪ 带我飞向月球 ♪
♪ And let me play among the stars♪
♪ 让我在群星间嬉戏♪
♪ Let me see what spring is like♪
♪ 让我看看春天是怎样的♪
♪ On Jupiter and Mars♪
♪ 在木星和火星上♪
♪ In other words♪
♪ 换句话说♪
♪ Please be true♪
♪ 请真诚以待 ♪
♪ In other words♪
♪ 换句话说 ♪
♪ I love you♪
♪ 我爱你 ♪
What do we do?
我们该怎么办？
Find survivors.
寻找幸存者。
And get that ELT beacon.
并取回那个应急定位信标。
- Becky. - I think I've got a pulse.
- 贝基。 - 我好像摸到脉搏了。
Becky.
贝基。
Come on.
快点。
Becky, wake up!
贝基，醒醒！
We have to move right now!
我们得马上行动！
Becky! Water's rising.
贝基！水涨上来了。
Can you move her?
你能挪动她吗？
She's, like, 150 pounds.
她大概有 150 磅重。
I've only got the use of one arm and I got to get all the way up there?
我只有一只胳膊能使上劲，还得一路爬到那么高的地方？
150 pounds? Really?
150 磅？真的吗？
I'm a... grandmother.
我是个……奶奶。
The one I'm gonna help is this little fellow here.
我要帮的是这个小家伙。
- Let's go. - I can climb.
- 走吧。 - 我自己能爬。
I'm a good climber. Show us your stuff, hotshot.
我爬得很棒。露一手吧，小能手。
Okay. Yep.
好的。是的。
How long before they find us?
他们多久能找到我们？
Could be an hour or several hours.
可能一个小时，也可能几个小时。
That's if they got the signal.
前提是他们收到了信号。
"If"?
“如果”？
If the ELT activated when we went down.
如果我们坠机时应急定位发射器启动了。
And if it didn't?
如果没启动呢？
Yeah.
是啊。
That's why I'm going for a little swim.
所以我打算去游一会儿。
It's in the midsection.
就在腹部位置。
I'd take the raft, but you might need it.
我本想带上救生筏，但你可能用得着。
Let me go.
让我走吧。
Waikiki Roughwater. Three times.
威基基粗浪游泳赛。三次。
I can do this, okay? Trust me.
我能做到，好吗？相信我。
Yeah. Where are you going?
嗯……你要去哪儿？
Um... To the middle of the plane.
呃……去飞机中部。
Are my mom and dad there?
我爸妈在吗？
I want to come.
我想来。
Well, I have to swim, sweetheart.
亲爱的，我得去游泳。
I can swim. It's too far.
我会游泳。但距离太远了。
Okay? But I will look for your parents, I promise.
好的？但我会去找你的父母，我保证。
And my little brother, Finn.
还有我的弟弟，芬恩。
His name is Finn.
他叫芬恩。
Penny.
佩妮。
When you get out there, signal to confirm... Okay.
到达现场后，发出信号确认... 好的。
...that the ELT is working, all right?
...确认应急定位发射器正常工作，明白吗？
This goes in the log, right?
这个要记入日志，对吧？
Good enough for purser. Chief Purser.
对乘务长来说够用了。首席乘务长。
Here, take this. No, it'll just slow me down.
拿着这个。不，它会拖慢我。
Hey. Can you hold on to these for me until I get back?
嘿。能不能帮我保管这些，等我回来？
Thanks.
谢了。
It's in the overhead, starboard side, row 20.
就在头顶行李舱里，右侧，20 排。
Okay.
好的。
Just hit the switch and make sure the light stays on, okay?
按下开关，确保灯一直亮着，好吗？
Hey, good luck.
嘿，祝你好运。
We're gonna find your family, Cora.
我们会找到你家人的，科拉。
Okay?
还好吗？
You can do it, Becky.
你能行的，贝基。
Right behind you, hotshot.
就在你后面呢，大忙人。
It's this big lug I'm worried about.
我担心的是这个大家伙。
Right. Great.
好的，太好了。
Now I got Shelley Winters talking shit, huh?
现在连谢莉·温特斯都在说我的闲话了，是吧？
- Let me see that. - Hold still.
- 让我看看。 - 别动。
Put your hand here, okay?
把手放在这里，好吗？
Sir.
先生。
Shark.
鲨鱼。
Shark! Shark!
鲨鱼！鲨鱼！
Shark! Penny!
鲨鱼！佩妮！
Penny, shark!
佩妮，有鲨鱼！
Penny!
佩妮！
No!
别去！
Shark! Penny!
有鲨鱼！佩妮！
Penny! Shark!
佩妮！有鲨鱼！
Shark! Put this on.
鲨鱼！快穿上这个！
Shark!
鲨鱼！
Wait, the shoes. The shoes.
等等，我的鞋！我的鞋！
Come on.
来吧。
Keep your hands out of the water.
手别碰水。
No! Stop!
不！住手！
What? Isn't this how we get out?
怎么？难道这不是我们出去的办法吗？
Deploy the raft? We are in an air bubble.
部署救生筏？我们在气泡里呢。
Break the seal and then we sink.
打破密封圈，我们就会沉下去。
But...
但是……
Yeah, okay, okay. Yeah.
好吧，好吧，知道了。
Five.
五。
Sorry. Okay.
抱歉。好的。
Penny!
佩妮！
Penny! Shark!
佩妮！有鲨鱼！
Penny!
佩妮！
Shark in the water!
水里有鲨鱼！
We're coming!
我们来了！
Penny!
佩妮！
Penny! Shark!
佩妮！有鲨鱼！
Help me!
救命啊！
Penny!
佩妮！
Penny! Penny, we're coming! We're coming!
佩妮！佩妮，我们来了！我们来了！
Come on! Give me your hand!
来吧！把手给我！
Penny.
潘妮。
- We're sinking. - Where the hell are we?
- 我们正在下沉。- 我们他妈的到底在哪儿？
We are sinking.
我们在下沉。
What the... You have a huge cut.
天哪……你身上有道很深的伤口。
Let me help you. It's nothing.
让我帮你。让我帮你。不碍事。
Swim to me! Swim to me!
游向我！快游向我！
Here. I've got you!
来，我扶住你了！
Come here.
过来。
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
How's that feel?
感觉怎么样？
Less terrible.
没那么糟。
Thank you for fixing me up.
谢谢你帮我包扎。
And I'm sorry about the door thing.
还有，关于门的事，我很抱歉。
Yeah.
嗯。
We are gonna be okay.
我们会没事的。
We've got to calm this one down.
我们得让这位冷静下来。
Otherwise we're gonna run out of air, and terribly soon.
否则我们很快就会耗尽空气。
Hey, hey, little man.
嘿，嘿，小家伙。
You flying with your family?
你和家人一起飞吗？
My mommy and my new daddy and my sister, Cora.
我妈妈、新爸爸，还有我妹妹科拉。
Okay, well, we're gonna help you find your family.
好的，我们会帮你找到家人的。
I'm Matt. That's Becky.
我是马特，那是贝基。
And this is... Zoe.
这位是……佐伊。
Zoe. Zoe.
佐伊。佐伊。
And you are?
请问您是？
My name is Finn. Finn.
我叫芬恩。芬恩。
It's gonna be all right. It's gonna be okay.
一切都会好起来的。一切都会没事的。
Stop saying that when you know it's not true!
别再说这种明知不真实的话了！
We have to move back. Guys!
我们得搬回去。各位！
We have to move back.
我们得搬回去。
Shut up, Esports.
闭嘴，电竞小子。
What do you know about anything?
你懂什么？
There's too much weight up here.
这里的负担太重了。
Help us.
帮帮我们。
Open your eyes, dumbass.
睁开眼，蠢货。
Can't you see the steward's totally fried?
你没看到空乘完全吓傻了吗？
Just leave her alone, okay? She's in shock.
别管她了，行吗？她吓懵了。
Let me help you, okay?
让我来帮你，好吗？
Are you a doctor? No, I'm a veterinarian.
你是医生吗？不，我是兽医。
Great.
太好了。
Put a cone on her. Stop her from licking herself.
给她戴上伊丽莎白圈，别让她舔自己。
See, that's why I prefer animals to humans.
看吧，这就是为什么比起人类我更喜欢动物。
We don't have much time.
我们时间不多了。
Shut up. Just shut up.
闭嘴。给我闭嘴。
- We will sink. - We are all going to die!
- 我们会沉下去的。 - 我们都要死了！
What do you expect us to do?
你指望我们做什么？
Move back.
后退。
To where? In the water.
退到哪里？水里吗。
Take some weight off.
减轻点重量。
The kid's right. There's a coral reef under us.
那孩子说得对。我们下面有片珊瑚礁。
It might take some pressure off it.
这或许能减轻一些压力。
You go then.
那你先上吧。
One person won't make a difference.
一个人改变不了什么。
What'd you just call me?
你刚才叫我什么？
What did he call me? All right, all right!
他叫我什么？好吧，好吧！
Knock it off, both of you.
你们两个，别闹了。
Esport is right.
埃斯波特说得对。
Now, come on.
好了，来吧。
Anybody else coming?
还有其他人要来吗？
Huh?
嗯？
- Whoa! - Hold up, Jesse. What?
- 哇！ - 等等，杰西。什么？
If this thing goes down, anyone's who's down there is gonna be stuck inside.
如果这东西掉下去，下面的人都会被困在里面。
Okay?
好吗？
Jesse, don't be stupid, bro.
杰西，别犯傻，老兄。
Some of these wounded and old people won't make it out there, man.
这些伤者和老人里，有些人撑不到外面的，兄弟。
Jesse, come back here. Jesse.
杰西，回来。杰西。
Let's go. Come on, come on.
走吧。快点，快点。
Everyone's going. Yeah, everyone's going.
大家都走了。是啊，大家都走了。
Go for it.
上吧。
Just breathe.
深呼吸。
Guess you ain't getting me that vodka soda anytime soon.
看来你一时半会儿是没法给我弄杯伏特加苏打水了。
Coach!
教练！
I got you!
我接住你了！
- Are you hurt? - Lisa. Lisa.
- 你受伤了吗？ - 丽莎。丽莎。
Lisa! Lisa.
丽莎！丽莎。
Is there anyone else?
还有其他人吗？
Coach! Coach!
教练！教练！
Coach!
教练！
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
Grab him, Jesse! Grab him!
抓住他，杰西！抓住他！
Move! Move!
快动！快动！
Coach! Jesse!
教练！杰西！
Come on.
来吧。
Hey, hey. Take it easy.
嘿，嘿。放轻松点。
You.
你。
Get in the water! Take it easy. Take it easy.
下水去！放轻松点。放轻松点。
- No, stop. - Get in the water!
- 不，住手！ - 下水去！
- No! - Get in... I didn't know! Get in the water!
- 不！ - 下去……我不知道！下水去！
Stop it! Stop it!
住手！住手！
Stop it! Stop it, please!
住手！求你了，住手！
Stop it! Hey! Hey!
住手！嘿！嘿！
How is this helping? Huh?
这有什么用？嗯？
Do you want to live?
你想活吗？
Do you?
想吗？
Yes. Yes.
是的。是的。
Then we need to keep our cool.
那我们得保持冷静。
Tell me we're gonna keep our cool.
告诉我我们会保持冷静。
I'm gonna keep my cool.
我会保持冷静的。
- Kid, have some nuts. - Good protein.
- 孩子，吃点坚果。 - 优质蛋白质。
Growing boys need their protein.
正在长身体的男孩需要补充蛋白质。
Mommy says nuts make me fat.
妈妈说吃坚果会让我发胖。
What kind of a mother would say a thing like that?
什么样的母亲会说出这种话？
Okay, fine. Screw the nuts.
好吧，行。去他的螺母。
How old are you anyway?
你究竟多大了？
How much air do you think we have left?
你觉得我们还有多少氧气？
Almost eight.
快八小时了。
- You're seven. - It's too risky.
- 你七岁了。 - 这太冒险了。
I presume fully potty-trained.
我猜你已经完全学会上厕所了。
What, so just do nothing?
什么，就这么干等着？
The doors stay shut.
门一直锁着。
How old do you think I am? A hundred.
你觉得我多大年纪？一百岁。
Pretty close.
差不多。
Nobody is going to find us if we stay in here.
要是我们一直待在这儿，没人会找到我们。
Oh, great job, guys.
哦，干得漂亮，各位。
- Huh? - It's already getting stuffy.
- 嗯？ - 已经有点闷热了。
We could swim.
我们可以游泳。
I can go first, - swim down and find a way out. - No.
我可以先下去， - 游到下面找出口。 - 不行。
No, not on my watch. I can do it.
不行，在我值班期间绝不允许。让我来。
I know the plane better than you.
我比你更了解这架飞机。
And you have a broken wrist.
而你的手腕还断着。
Which you made better, remember?
是你治好的，记得吗？
Here, strap it.
来，绑上。
Come on.
来吧。
We don't have much time. Come on.
我们时间不多了。快点儿。
Okay. So, I'm gonna take a look around and then I'm gonna be back in a tick, okay?
好的。那我先四处看看，一会儿就回来，行吗？
Yeah? Yeah.
嗯？嗯。
Okay. Good.
好的。很好。
Don't go.
别走。
Hey, Finn.
嘿，芬恩。
You look after the ladies for me while I'm gone, yeah?
我不在的时候，替我照顾好女士们，好吗？
Okay, okay, okay.
好，好，好。
Hurry back... Matt.
快点回来……马特。
She remembered my name. Huh?
她记得我的名字。嗯？
Look, I've got a good feeling about us.
听着，我对我们俩很有信心。
Hey, hey!
嘿，嘿！
Hey, over here!
嘿，这边！
Help us!
快来帮帮我们！
Help! Over here!
救命！这边！
There's people that need help! Help!
有人需要帮助！救命！
My daughter, Cora.
我的女儿，科拉。
Help!
救命！
- Help! - How could this happen?
- 救命！ - 怎么会这样？
We're in the middle of nowhere.
我们身处荒郊野外。
How do you just fall out of the sky?
你怎么会从天上掉下来？
How long till they rescue us?
他们还要多久才能来救我们？
- Don't be a smart-ass. - Just answer the question.
- 别耍嘴皮子。 - 直接回答问题。
Look, I'll tell you what I know, okay?
听着，我把我知道的告诉你，行了吧？
Probably your fucking fault.
八成又是你的错。
You and this shitty airline.
你和这家破航空公司。
Look, you're angry, you want answers.
听着，你很生气，想要个说法。
You're gonna get them, okay?
你会得到的，好吗？
Truth is, we're lucky to be alive to blame somebody.
说实话，我们还能活着找人算账，已经是万幸了。
There were 257 souls on this flight.
这趟航班上有 257 条生命。
I count, maybe, 30 of us.
我数了数，大概只有我们 30 个人。
The way I see it, we have one job to do, and that is to get home to see our families.
在我看来，我们只有一个任务，那就是平安回家，见到我们的家人。
Okay, we have rafts. We need to get in them.
好了，我们有救生筏。我们得上去。
If you don't have a life jacket, take one from under a seat.
如果没有救生衣，请从座位下方取出一件。
Tell me your name. I'm Hutch.
告诉我你的名字。我是哈奇。
Hutch, I need you to pull out that second raft.
哈奇，我需要你把第二艘救生筏拉出来。
Everybody, help Hutch get the raft into the water.
大家，帮哈奇把救生筏放到水里。
It's stuck! It's stuck!
卡住了！卡住了！
Here, hold on to that.
来，抓住这个。
Cora, I need you to stay here, okay?
科拉，你得待在这里，好吗？
Stay away from the edge, all right?
离边缘远点，明白吗？
Okay.
好的。
I'm gonna go get something.
我去拿点东西。
Hey, everybody, be careful. The tide is moving fast.
嘿，大家小心点。潮水涨得很快。
Two, there...
二，那边……
All right, here we go. Ready?
好了，我们开始吧。准备好了吗？
I think we got it.
我觉得我们搞定了。
All right, ready? Ready?
好了，准备好了吗？准备好了吗？
Daddy.
爸爸。
Daddy!
爸爸！
Hey, come back! We need this! Let's go, let's go.
嘿，回来！我们需要这个！快走，快走。
Go. Go, go, go. Let's go. Let's get out of here.
走。快走，快走。我们走。我们离开这里。
Anybody, please, help me!
有人吗，求求你们，帮帮我！
Come on, baby.
来吧，宝贝。
We got this. Ready?
我们能行。准备好了吗？
Go, go, go.
冲，冲，冲。
We got this. One, two, three!
我们能行。一、二、三！
- Pull! - Daddy!
- 拉！ - 爸爸！
- Cora! - Pull!
- 科拉！ - 拉！
Get this onto a raft, don't drop it.
把这个放到木筏上，别掉了。
- Daddy! - Cora!
- 爸爸！ - 科拉！
- Let's get out of here. - Daddy, I'm sorry!
- 我们快离开这儿。 - 爸爸，对不起！
Cora! Cora! Come on. I'm sorry!
科拉！科拉！快走。对不起！
Get away from there! No, man, what are you doing?
离那儿远点！不，伙计，你在干什么？
Why didn't it open?
为什么打不开？
I don't know, pull the goddamn rope!
我不知道，快拉那该死的绳子！
Come on, come on.
快点，快点。
Come on.
加油。
Hey!
嘿！
Here!
这里！
The ELT.
应急定位发射器。
What?
什么？
The locator. That box I gave you. Where is it?
定位器。我给你的那个盒子。它在哪？
You gotta be kidding me.
你是在跟我开玩笑吧。
Come on, man, I was counting on you.
拜托，兄弟，我还指望你呢。
All you had to do was get it on the raft.
你只要把它弄到救生筏上就行。
Yeah, well, if it was so important, maybe you should've looked after it.
是啊，要是这东西真那么重要，你也许该自己看好它。
Locater? What's he talking about?
定位器？他在说什么？
Is that what they need to find us?
那是他们用来找我们的东西吗？
And you lost it?
你把它弄丢了？
Hey, don't put this on me, man.
嘿，别把责任推给我，老兄。
This was your responsibility, - Captain. - Hey!
这是你的责任，机长。 - 嘿！
- Over there! - Hey!
- 在那边！ - 嘿！
Here! Do you see them?
这里！你看到他们了吗？
Please, do something. No way.
拜托，想想办法。没门。
No, they can swim to the other raft.
不，他们可以游到另一个木筏上。
The current is too strong. They'll never make it.
水流太急了。他们根本过不去。
Can't you see we're already taking on water?
你没看到我们已经进水了吗？
Whoa... What... What... Oh, my God!
哇……什么……什么……哦，天哪！
Who the hell are you to decide?
你算老几，凭什么替我做决定？
I'm the captain. It's my plane.
我是机长，这是我的飞机。
Oh, that plane?
哦，那架飞机？
Great job. Huh?
干得漂亮，是吧？
People are dead because of you.
这些人因你而死。
And now you want to risk our lives to make yourself feel better?
现在你还要拿我们的命去冒险，就为了让你自己心里好受点？
No way. We stay put.
没门。我们就待着不动。
You call yourself a captain, huh?
就你这样还自称机长？
You can't even pilot a raft.
你连木筏都开不了。
We're going to get them.
我们会抓到他们的。
You know damn well what will happen to those two young men if we don't.
你他妈很清楚，如果我们不这么做，那两个年轻人会有什么下场。
Untether these rafts.
解开这些救生筏。
No! Hey!
不！嘿！
He hit me.
他打了我。
You're a witness.
你是个目击者。
Shut up, bitch.
闭嘴，贱人。
You heard the lady.
你听到这位女士的话了。
- And stop rocking the raft. - Let's go.
- 别晃船了。 - 我们走。
I want to go.
我想走了。
How much longer do we have to stay here?
我们还得在这里待多久？
I hope Matt hasn't swum away with a mermaid.
但愿马特没跟美人鱼游走了。
He wouldn't leave us.
他不会丢下我们的。
What's it waiting for?
还在等什么？
Let's get out of here.
我们离开这里吧。
Give me your hand. Come on.
把手给我。快。
Come on!
来吧！
Come on, come on, come on.
快点，快点，快点。
You two again, huh?
又是你们两个，嗯？
All right, let's get out of here.
好了，我们走吧。
Let's go.
走吧。
When we get outside the plane, we inflate our jackets.
等我们出了飞机，就充气穿上救生衣。
They'll take us straight up to the surface like a big balloon.
它们会像大号气球一样，直接把我们带到水面上。
No, I need a little more time.
不，我还需要一点时间。
You can't stay here.
你不能待在这里。
I can't take both of you. You can do it.
我不能同时带你们两个。你能做到的。
Doing this, doing that.
做这个，做那个。
I'm always trying to keep doing.
我总在努力继续做下去。
Ever since Bill died, it just gets old, you know?
自从比尔去世后，一切都变得索然无味，你明白吗？
Becky, I'm sorry. I am. But we have to go now.
贝基，我很抱歉。真的。但我们现在必须走了。
No, I know. You take Finn.
不，我知道。你带芬恩去吧。
No! You come, too. Please.
不行！你也一起来。求你了。
You stay strong, hotshot.
坚持住，王牌飞行员。
I admire your style. Don't worry about me.
我欣赏你的作风。别担心我。
I will come back, Becky. I promise.
我会回来的，贝琪。我保证。
You okay? Yeah?
你还好吗？真的吗？
Good boy.
好孩子。
Matt!
马特！
We can make it.
我们能赶上的。
So, Captain, do you have a plan that doesn't rely on just dumb luck?
那么，机长，你有没有什么计划不是光靠运气就能行？
You know, we're alive.
你知道吗，我们都还活着。
We're all alive.
我们都还活着。
You got kids?
你有孩子吗？
Yeah.
有。
My daughter, Terri.
我的女儿，泰瑞。
My little boy, Sean.
我的小儿子，肖恩。
Well, I got three.
嗯，我有三个孩子。
Youngest is five.
最小的五岁。
I can tell you they ain't growing up without me.
我可以告诉你，他们不可能在没有我的情况下长大。
So, whatever you gotta do to make yourself feel better about losing all those people back there... but don't use me, pal.
所以，不管你做什么来让自己对失去那些人感觉好受些……但别利用我，伙计。
Because I'm going home... whatever it takes.
因为我要回家……不惜一切代价。
Yeah, I am sure your kids are real proud of you.
是啊，我敢肯定你的孩子们一定为你感到骄傲。
No wonder you're single.
难怪你单身。
A plane!
飞机！
Plane is here. Hey!
飞机来了。嘿！
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
Hey!
嘿！
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
Down here, you asshole!
下面，你这混蛋！
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
Hey!
嘿！
Did they see us?
他们看见我们了吗？
They saw us, all right.
他们当然看见我们了。
We just gotta hold on.
我们得坚持住。
Zoe!
佐伊！
Zoe, wake up!
佐伊，醒醒！
Somebody help!
来人啊！
快来人啊！
My dear little Bella.
我亲爱的小贝拉。
I don't know why I'm doing this.
我不知道自己为什么要这么做。
You're never going to hear me.
你永远也听不到我的声音。
There's no service.
这里没有信号。
Bella...
贝拉……
I'm going to have a little chat with God... and ask him to fill your life with as much...
我要和上帝小小谈一谈……请求他让你的生命，也充满……
joy...
快乐……
as you've given me.
就像你给予我的那样。
Guam, Red Tail 24.
关岛，红尾 24 号 24。
Any updates on the transport situation?
运输情况有最新进展吗？
Working on it.
正在处理中。
We've got a Chinese trawler in the area.
该区域有一艘中国拖网渔船。
Red Tail 24, standby.
红尾 24 号，请待命。
Copy that.
收到。
This is the Xing Yang Yuan Yu 08.
这里是兴阳园渔 08 号。
Captain, we are enacting the 1974 SOLAS convention.
船长，我们正在执行 1974 年《国际海上人命安全公约》。
There's been a commercial airliner crash.
有一架商用客机坠毁了。
Your ship is closest to the area where we believe there are survivors in need of assistance.
你的船最靠近我们认为有需要救援的幸存者的区域。
Copy, Commander.
收到，指挥官。
What?
什么？
Thank you.
谢谢。
Just tell her.
直接告诉她吧。
That you're crazy about her.
告诉她你为她着迷。
I can't break team rules.
我不能违反团队规定。
What team rule?
什么团队规定？
Players cannot date each other.
选手之间不能约会。
My God.
我的天啊。
You're such an idiot.
你真是个白痴。
No one listens to that rule.
没人遵守那条规矩。
Just tell her.
直接告诉她吧。
Hey, Cora.
嘿，科拉。
Drink this.
把这个喝了。
They're not here.
他们不在这儿。
Hey. They left me.
嘿，他们丢下我了。
Come on.
别这样。
They didn't leave you.
他们没有丢下你。
My dad told me to look after my little brother.
我爸让我照顾好我弟弟。
I was horrible.
我太糟糕了。
I don't hate him.
我不恨他。
I know.
我知道。
He's seven.
他才七岁。
My son is seven.
我儿子七岁了。
That's Sean, there on the right.
那是肖恩，右边那个。
He's not seven.
他不是七岁。
It's an old picture.
那是张旧照片。
Hmm?
嗯？
They'll never get to see how I turn out.
他们永远看不到我变成什么样了。
Hey, they'll know.
嘿，他们会知道的。
Parents always know.
父母总是知道的。
They're always with you, Cora.
它们永远与你同在，科拉。
Oh, yes. Oh, my God.
哦，是的。哦，天哪。
- Oh, my God! - Oh, hey.
- 哦，天哪！ - 哦，嘿。
Oh, my God. They're gonna rescue us.
哦，天哪。他们要来救我们了。
Hutch, look after Cora.
哈奇，照顾好科拉。
Over here! Hey, we're here!
这边！嘿，我们在这儿！
Guam, Red Tail 24, we have survivors.
关岛，红尾号 24，发现幸存者。
Dropping flares and putting swimmer in the water.
投放照明弹，并让潜水员入水。
Hey!
嘿！
Deploy swimmer.
部署游泳者。
Hey!
嘿！
No!
不！
- We're at the door. - Copy that. Good to go.
- 我们到门口了。 - 收到。准备就绪。
No!
不！
We see you.
我们看到你了。
No! No!
不！不！
No!
不！
I can't pull us up. Up, up, up!
我拉不起来了。拉起来，拉起来，拉起来！
Red Tail 24, everything all right?
红尾 24 号，一切正常吗？
Oh, my God!
哦，天哪！
Cut it loose. Cut it loose!
松开它！松开它！
- Get me out! - Get me out of the water!
- 救我出去！ - 快把我从水里拉出来！
Give me your hand.
把手给我。
Get me out!
救我出去！
Get me out of here!
让我离开这里！
No!
不！
Bastard!
混蛋！
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
I'm here!
我来了！
Hey! Hey!
嘿！嘿！
Why'd they stop?
他们怎么停了？
They can't get past the reef.
他们无法越过暗礁。
We need to go to them.
我们得去找他们。
How? Where are the paddles?
怎么去？桨在哪儿？
We don't have any paddles. We have no paddles.
我们没有桨。一把都没有。
So what now, Captain?
那么现在怎么办，机长？
The current will carry us to the deep water.
水流会把我们带到深水区。
Hey!
嘿！
The other rafts, they've got paddles.
其他救生筏都有桨。
They'll make it.
他们会成功的。
Where's Cora?
科拉在哪？
The little girl.
那个小女孩。
Cora? Cora? Cora?
科拉？科拉？科拉？
Is she in the water?
她在水里吗？
Cora? Cora?
科拉？科拉？
There she is! There!
她在那里！那里！
Look, look!
看，快看！
Hey! Cora!
嘿！科拉！
Cora, stay there!
科拉，待在那儿别动！
- Cora. - Cora!
- 科拉。 - 科拉！
We have to go get her.
我们得去接她。
The current's too strong.
水流太急了。
Well, the other raft's nearly there.
另一艘筏子快到了。
That plane's going to be in the water in 15 minutes.
那架飞机 15 分钟后就要坠入水中了。
All right, I'm gonna get her.
好吧，我去救她。
- The sharks. - Are you crazy?
- 鲨鱼们。 - 你疯了吗？
They're everywhere. No, it's your boat.
它们到处都是。不，是你的船。
Hey, no, wait!
嘿，不，等等！
No.
不。
Swim fast! Swim faster!
游快点！再游快点！
- He can make it. - He's gonna make it.
- 他能行。 - 他一定能行。
Help me!
救命！
I am an American!
我是美国人！
He made it! Yes!
他成功了！太棒了！
Yes!
太棒了！
Cora, hey.
科拉，嘿。
Cora, look at me.
科拉，看着我。
Hey.
嘿。
Cora, we're gonna go for a swim.
科拉，我们要去游泳了。
Together. You and me.
一起。你和我。
I want to stay here with my daddy.
我想和爸爸待在这里。
You can't stay here, Cora.
你不能待在这里，科拉。
We gotta take a little detour, okay?
我们得稍微绕个路，好吗？
The water's rising, Cora.
水位在上涨，科拉。
Your daddy wants you to be a brave girl, okay?
你爸爸希望你能做个勇敢的女孩，好吗？
All right, let's put this on you.
好了，把这个给你戴上。
Okay? There you go.
好了吗？戴好了。
We're gonna be all right, Cora.
我们会没事的，科拉。
We got this, okay?
我们能搞定的，好吗？
I'm gonna put this belt on over my neck, around my back, okay?
我会把这条腰带绕过脖子，缠在背上，明白吗？
And I want you to hold onto it while we swim. All right?
游泳的时候你要抓紧它，好吗？
You're not gonna let go of this, okay?
你绝对不能松手，知道吗？
You hold on tight. Okay.
抓紧了。好的。
Hey, we're drifting away.
嘿，我们正在漂远。
We're drifting away, we're drifting away from them.
我们正在漂远，离他们越来越远了。
- Wrong way, dumbass. - To the boat!
- 方向错了，蠢货。 - 往船那边去！
Grab the belt, Cora. Grab it.
抓住安全带，科拉。快抓住。
Shark! Shark!
鲨鱼！鲨鱼！
They all left.
他们都走了。
Why'd they go?
他们为什么走了？
God only knows.
天知道。
- It's okay, it's okay. - Everything's okay.
- 没事的，没事的。 - 一切都会好的。
It's gonna be okay.
会没事的。
I think they're gone.
我想他们走了。
- We'll be okay.
- 我们会没事的。
Yeah.
有。
You son of a bitch.
你这混蛋。
- Oh, my God!
- 哦，我的天哪！
- Here, Cora. - Let's put this around you.
- 来，科拉。 - 我们把这个给你披上。
A little detour. Huh?
稍微绕了点路。是吧？
Yeah.
是啊。
A little detour.
一个小小的绕道。
- Hey! - Hey, we got a signal.
- 嘿！ - 嘿，我们有信号了。
- We got reception. - Ben, we got reception!
- 我们收到信号了。 - 本，我们有信号了！
The phones are working!
手机能用了！
The pet chip. Your phone?
宠物芯片。你的手机呢？
Can you see your phone?
你能看到你的手机吗？
Can I see it?
我能看看吗？
Password's his birthday.
密码是他的生日。
There. See?
看到了吧？
Thank you, Captain.
谢谢，机长。
We owe your crew for everything you've done for us.
我们非常感谢您的机组为我们所做的一切。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Raft. Over there.
木筏。在那边。
Where's my brother?
我弟弟在哪？
He's gotta be here.
他一定在这里。
The tracker says he's here.
追踪器显示他在这里。
Finn?
芬恩？
I'm sorry, Cora.
对不起，科拉。
Finn.
芬恩。
Finn! Finn!
芬恩！芬恩！
Zoe! Finn!
佐伊！芬恩！
Finn, Finn!
芬恩，芬恩！
We made it.
我们成功了。
Cora! Finn! Finn!
科拉！芬恩！芬恩！
Come on. There you go.
来吧。这就对了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
It's okay, Cora.
没关系，科拉。
Becky? Becky?
贝基？贝基？
She's waiting for me.
她在等我。
Come on, let's get her up.
来，我们扶她起来。
- Ben? - It's me.
- 本？ - 是我。
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
天哪，你还好吗？
Yeah. I thought we lost you.
是啊，我们还以为你挺不过来了。
I'm okay.
我没事。
- Ben... - Let me talk to him!
- 本... - 让我跟他谈谈！
Sean... Oh, my God.
肖恩...哦，我的天啊。
Dad's on the phone right now.
爸爸正在接电话。
Daddy, are you there?
爸爸，你在吗？
I'm here, Sean. I'm right here.
我在，肖恩。我就在这儿。
Where are you?
你在哪儿？
I'm coming home.
我要回家了。
- Mom, he's coming home. - He's coming home!
- 妈，他要回家了。 - 他要回家了！
I told you he would, darling.
我跟你说过他会回来的，亲爱的。
I love you, Dad.
我爱你，爸爸。
- I love you, too, son. - I love all of you.
- 我也爱你，儿子。- 我爱你们所有人。